A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records of the JDR 3rd Fund, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1989; 1
    - Director's Office, 1955, 1957-1989; 3
      - Asian Individuals, 1955, 1957, 1959-1983; 4
        - K, 1962-1981
          - Kamalakshi, M. J., 1975, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 662)
          - Kamat, Ravindra S., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 663)
          - Kameda, Tsutomu & Chimyo Horioka, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 664)
          - Kamiya, Koji, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 665)
          - Kamtorn, Snidvongs, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 666)
          - Kanade, N. N., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 667)
          - Kanazawa, Masakata, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 668)
          - Kanesaka, Kenji (Box 25, Folder 669)
          - Kang, Eun Yup, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 670)
          - Kang, Wha Ja, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 671)
          - Kang, Yu-jung, 1970, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 672)
          - Kanvinde, A. P., 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 673)
          - Kanvinde, Sunita, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 674)
          - Kao, Arthur Mu-Sen, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 675)
          - Kao, Grace Mei Sheung, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 676)
          - Kao, Kelly, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 677)
          - Kapadia, Chandrasen, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 678)
          - Kapoor, Bhatwan, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 679)
          - Kapur, Geeta, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 680)
          - Kapur, Indrani, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 681)
          - Kara, Juro, 1969-1970, 1972, 1975, 1978, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 682)
          - Kartiwa, Suwati, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 683)
          - Kashyap, Prakruti, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 684)
          - Kasim, Normal, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 685)
          - Katatikarn, Suchada, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 686)
          - Katatikarn, Suchada, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 686A)
          - Kathuria, Y., 1978 (Box 26, Folder 687)
          - Kato, Kuniko Lucy, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 688)
          - Kawahara, Yoshio, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 689)
          - Kawai, Yoshihiro, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 690)
          - Kawakita, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 691)
          - Kawashima, Takashi, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 692)
          - Kayam, Umar, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 693)
          - Kazi, Cham-Kusho, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 694)
          - Kazi, Soman T., 1969 (Box 26, Folder 695)
          - Keau, Yiu Phing, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 696)
          - Kee, Casey, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 697)
          - Kei, Kawakami, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 698)
          - Kelker, Yeshawant, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 699)
          - Khairzada, Faiz M., 1964-1966, 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 700)
          - Khalid, Mohamad Nor, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 701)
          - Khan, Amir, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 702)
          - Khan, Luthfullah, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 703)
          - Khan, Mohammad Ishtiaq, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 704)
          - Khandalavala, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 705)
          - Khanna, Bishamber, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 706)
          - Khanna, Krishen, 1962-1969, 1971, 1974, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 707)
          - Khanna, Risika, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 708)
          - Khatau, Abhay, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 709)
          - Khatun, M., 1968 (Box 26, Folder 710)
          - Khawaja, Fawad M., 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 711)
          - Khobragade, Ambadas V., 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 712)
          - Khoo, Joo Ee, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 713)
          - Khoo, Khay Tat, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 714)
          - Khoury, Sari I., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 715)
          - Khunnamart, Viraj (Box 26, Folder 716)
          - Khunnavat, Supadee, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 717)
          - Khurana, Bhim Sain, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 718)
          - Kiang, Yu-lung, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 719)
          - Kibria, Mohamad, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 720)
          - Kikuchi, Masabumi, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 721)
          - Kim, Baek-Bong (Box 26, Folder 722)
          - Kim, Byung-mo, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 723)
          - Kim, Chewon, 1967-1968, 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 724)
          - Kim, Choung-za, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 725)
          - Kim, Chung Sook, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 726)
          - Kim, Hachul, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 727)
          - Kim, Hanjue Oh, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 728)
          - Kim, Hanjue Oh, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 728A)
          - Kim, Hwan-soo, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 729)
          - Kim, Jeong-Ok, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 730)
          - Kim, Jong-Yong (Box 27, Folder 731)
          - Kim, Jung-bae, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 732)
          - Kim, Jung-bae, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 732A)
          - Kim, Keelhong, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 733)
          - Kim, Kwangjoo, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 734)
          - Kim, Madia, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 735)
          - Kim, Man Bok, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 736)
          - Kim, Se Chung, 1977, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 737)
          - Kim, Soung Tai (Box 27, Folder 738)
          - Kim, Soye, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 739)
          - Kim, Suk Soon, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 740)
          - Kim, Sun Joo, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 741)
          - Kim, Sun-Duk, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 742)
          - Kim, Sung Kyu, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 743)
          - Kim, Sung-Ja, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 744)
          - Kim, Tai Soo, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 745)
          - Kim, Won-Tae, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 746)
          - Kim, Youngna, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 747)
          - Kim, Youngna, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 747A)
          - Kimura, Yokiko, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 748)
          - Kinoshita, Yoko, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 749)
          - Kit, Chang Ying, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 750)
          - Kitagawa, Toshiharu, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 751)
          - Kitakizaki, Takashi, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 752)
          - Kitamura, Mitsuo, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 753)
          - Kiyooka, Sumiko, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 754)
          - Kobayashi, Fumio, 1970, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 755)
          - Kobayashi, Kenji Keritani (Box 27, Folder 756)
          - Koh, Jolly, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 757)
          - Koh, You-Ching Eric, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 758)
          - Kohzad, Mohammad Nabi, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 759)
          - Koizumi, Kashiro (Box 27, Folder 760)
          - Kojiro, Yuichiro, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 761)
          - Komatsu, Hideko, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 762)
          - Komolthiti, Pacharee (Box 27, Folder 763)
          - Komuro, Itaru, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 764)
          - Kon, Noriko, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 765)
          - Kondo, Hajime, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 766)
          - Kong, Shee-Chong, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 767)
          - Koppar, D. H., 1969, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 768)
          - Koshi, Koichi, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 769)
          - Kow, Choong Kam, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 770)
          - Krataithong, Kamthronthep, 1972-1973, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 771)
          - Krishna, Anand, 1967, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 772)
          - Krishnadasa, Rai, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 773)
          - Krishnamurti, Yamini, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 774)
          - Ku, Hi-so, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 775)
          - Ku, Ping-Hsing, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 776)
          - Kulkarni, D. V., 1974 (Box 27, Folder 777)
          - Kulkarni, K. S., 1965, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 778)
          - Kulkarni, Mandakini, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 779)
          - Kulkarni, Maya, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 780)
          - Kulkarni, Shaila, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 781)
          - Kulsrethsiri, Sulyporn, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 782)
          - Kumar, Yogesh, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 783)
          - Kumasata, Naoco, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 784)
          - Kumatsu, Hideko, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 785)
          - Kundanmal, Prakash, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 786)
          - Kuno, Shin, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 787)
          - Kuo, Chiang-Shen, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 788)
          - Kuo, Paul, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 789)
          - Kurata, Bunsaku, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 790)
          - Kuroemon, Onoe, II, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 791)
          - Kurokawa, Naoki, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 792)
          - Kurosaki, Akira, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 793)
          - Kuruvikkattukuzhyil, John K. M., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 794)
          - Kusama, Yayoi, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 795)
          - Kusnadi, S. N., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 796)
          - Kussudiardja, Bagong, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 797)
          - Kusumi, Kenichi, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 798)
          - Kuwabara, Moriyuki, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 799)
          - Kuwabara, Sumio, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 800)
          - Kwak, Byong Kook, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 801)
          - Kwak, Sung, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 802)
          - Kwan, Ding On, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 803)
          - Kwan, Lawrence, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 804)
          - Kwon, Ok-yon, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 805)
        - L, 1959, 1961, 1963-1980
          - Lahira, Shanu, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 805)
          - Lai, Chi-Man, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 806)
          - Laine, John, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 807)
          - Lakshmi, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 808)
          - Lam, Flora, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 809)
          - Latifi, Shah Tawab, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 810)
          - Lau, Anthony, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 811)
          - Ledesma, Ligaya P., 1959, 1964, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 812)
          - Ledesma, Ligaya P., 1959, 1964, 1967-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 812A)
          - Lee, Ae Ju, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 813)
          - Lee, Bang-Eunn, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 814)
          - Lee, Chung-Ji, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 815)
          - Lee, Dai Keong, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 816)
          - Lee, Daiwon, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 817)
          - Lee, Dong Chan, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 818)
          - Lee, Dong Chan, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 818A)
            Restricted from scholarly access-material fragile
          - Lee, Dong-ju, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 819)
          - Lee, Du-Hyun, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 820)
          - Lee, Eugene (Yuh-chin), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 821)
          - Lee, Hi-Chang, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 822)
          - Lee, Hitai, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 823)
          - Lee, Hyo-young, 1967-1968, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 824)
          - Lee, In-Sook, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 825)
          - Lee, Inn Sang, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 826)
          - Lee, Jeong-Kuen, 1972, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 827)
          - Lee, Joo For, 1966-1967, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 828)
          - Lee, Joon Hee, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 829)
          - Lee, Kang-Up, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 830)
          - Lee, Key-sock, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 831)
          - Lee, Kian Seng, 1965-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 832)
          - Lee, Kian Seng, 1965-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 832A)
          - Lee, Kum Sing, 1959, 1961, 1963-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 833)
          - Lee, Kyungsook, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 834)
          - Lee, Lena, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 835)
          - Lee, Mabel, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 836)
          - Lee, Mary Kyunksook, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 837)
          - Lee, O-Nyoung, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 838)
          - Lee, Oh-Nyong, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 839)
          - Lee, Panda, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 840)
          - Lee, Sang-Man, 1971, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 841)
          - Lee, Se Duk, 1965, 1967, 1971-1976, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 842)
          - Lee, Sung-Jae, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 843)
          - Lee, Tien Pao-Tien, 1972, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 844)
          - Lee, Ting-Ting, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 845)
          - Lee, Tsun-I, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 846)
          - Lee, Yang-Won, 1975, 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 847)
          - Lee, Young, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 848)
          - Leesuwan, Viboon, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 849)
          - Legarda, Benito, Jr., 1966, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 850)
          - Lei, Roc Ta-Peng, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 851)
          - Leonardia, Amiel Y., 1971, 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 852)
          - Leong, Yan Sook, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 853)
          - Leung, Kui Ting, 1968, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 854)
          - Leung, Linda, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 855)
          - Lew, Jeanie, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 856)
          - Lhamo, Namgyal, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 857)
          - Li, Chu-tsing, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 858)
          - Li, Li-Tan, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 859)
          - Li, Mei-shu, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 860)
          - Li, Mingche M., 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 861)
          - Li, Mingche M., 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 861A)
          - Li, Stephen Ku Ching, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 862)
          - Li, Stephen Ku Ching, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 862A)
          - Li, Tai-Shiang, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 863)
          - Liao, Shiou-Ping, 1968-1970, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 864)
          - Liao, Wen-Li, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 865)
          - Lim, Eng Chye, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 866)
          - Lim, Hoong, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 867)
          - Lim, Sung Kyu, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 868)
          - Lim, Tong Juan, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 869)
          - Lin, Chia Li, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 870)
          - Lin, Erh, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 871)
          - Lin, Hwey-Lin, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 872)
          - Liu, Bennet, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 873)
          - Liu, Ding-Hwa Eddy, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 874)
          - Liu, Jackie Chia-Chi, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 875)
          - Liu, Judith Johns, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 876)
          - Liu, Kenneth, 1972, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 877)
          - Liu, Wen-san, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 878)
          - Lobo, Rex de Faunce, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 879)
          - Locsin, Leandro, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 880)
          - Loh, Mary, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 881)
          - Loke, King Loong, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 882)
          - Loke, King Loong, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 882A)
          - Lubis, Mochtar & Arman, 1962, 1968-1969, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 883)
          - Lui, Shiu Mui, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 884)
          - Lung, David, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 885)
          - Luong, Dat-ngoc, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 886)
          - Luz, Arturo R., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 887)
        - M, 1963-1980
          - Madnani, Rajkumar Ramchand, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 888)
          - Madnani, Rajkumar Ramchand, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 888A)
          - Mago, Pran Nath, 1965-1967 (Box 30, Folder 890)
          - Mago, Pran Nath, Photographs, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 891)
          - Mahedee, Rahul, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 892)
          - Mahadevan, T. K., 1971, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 893)
          - Mahammad, Isha, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 894)
          - Mahaparta, R. P., 1979 (Box 30, Folder 895)
          - Maira, Shakti, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 896)
          - Maita, Masafumi, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 897)
          - Maitra, Kalyani, 1971, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 898)
          - Majid, Mian A., 1965 (Box 31, Folder 899)
          - Makahekum, Abraham, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 900)
          - Malang Santos, Mauro, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 901)
          - Malhotra, K. K., 1972 (Box 31, Folder 902)
          - Malik, Keshev, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 903)
          - Malla, Kamal, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 904)
          - Mamiya, Michio, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 905)
          - Mamora, Alfendy Bontor, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 906)
          - Manalo, Noel, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 907)
          - Manandhar, Ramesh, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 908)
          - Manavalan, Vijay Mohan, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 909)
          - Mandar, Gani, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 910)
          - Mangahas, Ruby K., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 911)
          - Mangkudilaga, D. Sufwandi, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 912)
          - Marcelo, Severino, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 914)
          - Marasinghe, Eugene Walter, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 913)
          - Marquez, Marilyn G., 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 915)
          - Martin, Gavin, 1976, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 916)
          - Martin, Gavin, 1976, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 916A)
          - Martono, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 917)
          - Masaaki, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 918)
          - Mathur, N. L., 1969 (Box 31, Folder 919)
          - Matsubara, Naoko, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 920)
          - Matsuda, Kunihiro, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 921)
          - Matsudaira, Yoritushe, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 922)
          - Matsui, Akira, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 923)
          - Matsui, Kuniko, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 924)
          - Matsui, Kuniko, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 924A)
          - Matsutani, Takesada, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 925)
          - Maulana, Ireng, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 926)
          - Mayuyama, Junkichi, 1965-1966, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 927)
          - Mazumdar, Sanjoy, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 928)
          - McNally, Joseph, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 929)
          - Medina, Buenaventura S., Jr., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 930)
          - Mehrotra, Arvind Krishna, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 931)
          - Mehta, Chandravadan Chimanlal, 1964-1966, 1968-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 932)
          - Mehta, D. S., 1965-1966, 1968, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 933)
          - Mehta, Jaimini, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 934)
          - Mehta, Meera, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 935)
          - Mehta, Raksha, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 936)
          - Mehta, Rama, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 937)
          - Mehta, Sreelekekha, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 938)
          - Mehta, Ved, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 939)
          - Meishin, Siow, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 940)
          - Menon, Kannan, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 941)
          - Menon, Raghava, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 942)
          - Mercedes, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 943)
          - Merchant, Ismail, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 944)
          - Merh, Anjali Sukumar, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 945)
          - Miller, Harry, 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 946)
          - Minocha, Geeta, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 947)
          - Minoda, Norihiko, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 948)
          - Mirza, Mahmud, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 949)
          - Mishimi, Yukio, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 950)
          - Misra, R. N., 1979 (Box 32, Folder 951)
          - Misra, Soumya, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 952)
          - Mitamura, Haruo, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 953)
          - Mitra, Gopal, 1965, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 954)
          - Mitra, Pratip Kumar, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 955)
          - Mitra, S. B., 1975 (Box 32, Folder 956)
          - Miura, Naoyuki, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 957)
          - Miyata, Masako, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 958)
          - Miyamoto, Noriko, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 959)
          - Mizuno, Nirohiro, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 960)
          - Mockon, Josephine, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 961)
          - Modi, Rohit, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 962)
          - Modina, Fulceda M., 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 963)
          - Mohamedi, Nasreen, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 964)
          - Montalban, Ma. Divinagracia B., 1971 (Box 32, Folder 965)
          - Mookerjee, Ajit, 1963-1964, 1966-1969, 1971, 1974, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 966)
          - Mookerjee, Priya, 1971, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 967)
          - Mori, Toshio, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 968)
          - Moriguchi, Akira, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 969)
          - Muda, Kalsom, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 970)
          - Mudjanattistomo, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 971)
          - Mukherjee, B. N., 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 972)
          - Munakata, Kuniyoshi, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 973)
          - Munshi, Supriya, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 974)
          - Murabayashi, Miyuki, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 975)
          - Murase, Robert K., 1973 (Box 32, Folder 976)
          - Murdeyshwar, Shriniwas, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 977)
          - Murti, K. V. S., 1979 (Box 32, Folder 978)
          - Muter, Anak A., 1969 (Box 32, Folder 979)
          - Mutoh, Yasuyuki, 1975, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 980)
          - Mutoh, Yoshiyuki, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 981)
          - Mynak, Rimpoche, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 982)
          - Mynak, Tulku, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 983)
        - N, 1964, 1966-1980
          - Nagano, Shozo, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 984)
          - Nagare, Masayuki, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 985)
          - Nageswara, C. V., 1979 (Box 32, Folder 986)
          - Naik, Anandmohan, 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 987)
          - Naing, U Min, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 988)
          - Nair, S. M., 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 989)
          - Nakagawa, Ryoichi, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 990)
          - Nakagawa, Shigeo, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 991)
          - Nakahara, Yusuke, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 992)
          - Nakahashi, Kenji, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 993)
          - Nakajima, Akiko, 1969-1970, 1972-1973, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 994)
          - Nakamura, Hideki, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 995)
          - Nakamura, Keiji, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 996)
          - Nakamura, N., 1978 (Box 33, Folder 997)
          - Nakamura, Tatsuya, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 998)
          - Nakazawa, Fujiko, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 999)
          - Nakbua, Amphon, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 1000)
          - Naktong, Supachai, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1001)
          - Nam, Myung Ja, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1002)
          - Nambudiri, Krishnan, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 1003)
          - Namgyal, Chogyal Palden Thondup, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1004)
          - Nandi, Prakash Kumar, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 1005)
          - Nara, Hiroshi, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1006)
          - Naris, Day, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1007)
          - Nath, Amar, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1008)
          - Nath, Pandit Pran, 1969-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 1009)
          - Natu, K. S., 1970 (Box 33, Folder 1010)
          - Navarro, Edgardo, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1011)
          - Naveed, Sabahat, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1012)
          - Naweed, Abdullah, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1013)
          - Nawid, Senzil, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1014)
          - Nayyar, Harsh, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 1015)
          - Neak, Chen, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1016)
          - Neogy, Prithwish, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1017)
          - Ng, Lee Gek, 1964, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1018)
          - Ng, Lee Gek, 1964, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1018A)
          - Ngan, Amy, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1019)
          - Nii, Yoko, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1020)
          - Nikoonkam, Uaporn, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1021)
          - Nimnuals, Kosol, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1022)
          - Nimnuals, Kosol, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1022A)
          - Nirand, Pichai, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 1023)
          - Nitosastro, Santoso, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 1024)
          - Noda, Teryuki, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1025)
          - Noda, Tetsuya, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 1026)
          - Nojima, Minoru, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 1027)
          - Nomachi, Ryzuko, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1028)
          - Nor, Mustapha, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1029)
          - Norbu, Thubten Jigme, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 1030)
          - Norbu, Tsong-hongsang, Thupten, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1031)
          - Noronha, Nailsun, 1969-1973, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1032)
          - Nutukamarane, L., 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1033)
        - O, 1966-1972, 1974-1980
          - Oak, Anand Hari, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1034)
          - Oak, Kil-Sung, 1970, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1035)
          - Oaten, E. Kalmira, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1036)
          - Obeyesekere, Gananath, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1037)
          - Ocampo, Galo B., 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1038)
          - Oemartopo, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1039)
          - Oetoro, Bambang, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 1040)
          - Ogawa, Morihiro, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1041)
          - Ogawa, Toshiro, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1042)
          - Ogimo, Yoshikazu (Box 34, Folder 1043)
          - Oh, Byung Nam, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 1044)
          - Ohbayashi, Nobuhiko (Box 34, Folder 1045)
          - Ohri, Vishwa Chander, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 1046)
          - Ohtani, Koshin M., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1047)
          - Oi, Toshiyasu, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1048)
          - Oka, Iwataro, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 1049)
          - Okada, Masumi, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 1050)